[{"id":1,"text":"What the city capital in Israel?","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662301378634,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Tel-Aviv","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":true},{"id":3,"text":"Herzelia","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Haifa","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":2,"text":"What the city capital in Germany?","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Berlin","isCorrect":true},{"id":2,"text":"Minech","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"Dortmund","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Frankfurt","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":3,"text":"3 + 3 =","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"plus question","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662367921710,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"4","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"1","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"6","isCorrect":true},{"id":4,"text":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":4,"text":"7^2","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"square question","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"45","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"46","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"48","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"49","isCorrect":true}]},{"id":5,"text":"What result to next code","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","layout":true,"type":true,"language":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Berlin","isCorrect":true},{"id":2,"text":"Minech","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"Dortmund","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Frankfurt","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":6,"text":"What the city capital in Rusia?","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","layout":true,"type":true,"language":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Sant-Petzborg","isCorrect":true},{"id":2,"text":"Zenit","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"Moskva","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Kazan","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":7,"text":"What the city apital in Spain?","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Madrid","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"Valencia","isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"text":"Barcelona","isCorrect":true},{"id":4,"text":"Viadolid","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":8,"text":"What the city capital in Franch?","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Capital cities","layout":true,"type":false,"language":false,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662459512092,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"marcey","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"id":3,"text":"Monaco","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Paris","isCorrect":true}]},{"id":9,"text":"8 * 8 - 5 + 3","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"Invoice operation","type":true,"layout":true,"language":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662285618906,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"48","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"62","isCorrect":true},{"id":3,"text":"63","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"68","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":10,"text":"whats the top number in integer","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"C#","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662306436588,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"123456","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"2147483647","isCorrect":true},{"id":3,"text":"4325325","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"346436621","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":11,"text":"whats is javaScript","textBelowQuestion":"","tag":"JavaScript","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662306436588,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"Different name for java","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"Language for web developing","isCorrect":true},{"id":3,"text":"just a joke","isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"text":"Language C running on web","isCorrect":false}]},{"id":12,"text":"sdgdgs","textBelowQuestion":"dgsdgs","tag":"sdgdgs","type":true,"language":true,"layout":true,"isActivate":false,"lastUpdate":1662502368918,"Answers":[{"id":1,"text":"sdgdgs","isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"text":"dsgdgs","isCorrect":false}]}]